<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Review Topics on Hammond's Notes</title><link>https://jmhammond.github.io/calc/review/</link><description>Recent content in Review Topics on Hammond's Notes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://jmhammond.github.io/calc/review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Section 1.1</title><link>https://jmhammond.github.io/calc/review/section1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jmhammond.github.io/calc/review/section1/</guid><description>Section 1.1 - Four Ways of Representing a Function
Full disclosure: these videos are produced my another professor, and I&amp;rsquo;m including them here for review.
The following videos are lecture videos covering the material from Section 1.1 in Stewart&amp;rsquo;s Calculus 8th edition. Each major topic in the section is broken down into a short video.
The following video covers the fundamentals of functions including the basic definition and some visual examples.</description></item><item><title>Section 1.2</title><link>https://jmhammond.github.io/calc/review/section2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jmhammond.github.io/calc/review/section2/</guid><description>Section 1.2 - Mathematical Models: A Catalog of Essential Functions
The following videos are lecture videos covering the material from Section 1.2 in Stewart&amp;rsquo;s Calculus 8th edition. Each major topic in the section is broken down into a short video.
This first video discusses linear models and their associated linear functions.
The next video discusses polynomial functions, which are some of the nicest functions. The domain of any polynomial function is always all real numbers.</description></item><item><title>Section 1.3</title><link>https://jmhammond.github.io/calc/review/section3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jmhammond.github.io/calc/review/section3/</guid><description>Section 1.3 - New Functions from Old Functions
The following videos are lecture videos covering the material from Section 1.3 in Stewart&amp;rsquo;s Calculus 8th edition. Each major topic in the section is broken down into a short video.
In the first video we investigate the horizontal and vertical translations of functions and the corresponding algebraic relationships related to these geometric translations.
In the next video we discuss the horizontal and vertical stretching of a function and the related algebra.</description></item></channel></rss>